

Vijayalakshmi S, Yoga Instructor / Therapist

Experienced and passionate Yoga Instructor with over 3 years of teaching experience and advanced training in various yoga approaches. Through individual and group sessions I am committed to providing extensive instruction and counseling to my clients, while motivating them to find true inner peace and their healthiest self. Adept in creating powerful individually tailored teaching plans that aim to support and benefit each and every student. Bringing forth a love and respect for the art of yoga, and all that it encompasses for both body and soul.

Employment History

Yoga Instructor. at Indepedent Entreprenuer, Bengaluru

July 2020 — Present

- Masters in Yoga therapy from S-Vyasa: https://svyasa.edu.in/
- Enterpreneur teaching yoga both virtually and physically at studios
- Conducted yoga therapy for corporate programmes
- Conducted beginner and intermediate Yoga classes for members.
- Instructed Yoga practices to 300+ tailors virtually for madura-coats program-This is a non profit initiative to introduce yoga to members of this industry.
- Attended training workshops to ensure my teachings were on trend with the latest and most up to date fitness findings.

TV News Reader. at Multiple Channels, Chennai

March 2002 — January 2020

- TV news anchor for six TV channels based out of Chennai
- Primary channel was for Jaya TV and Podigai TV
- Also served as secondary news reader at Doordarshan channel

Radio Announcer. at All India Radio, Chennai

March 2004 — July 2014

Presented news and comments about salient events.

Education

Masters in Yoga therapy from S-Vyasa, https://svyasa.edu.in/, Bengaluru

March 2020 — June 2022

Teachers Training Diploma, SBGT, Salem

March 1990 — March 1992

Skills

Effective Lesson Planning

Knowledge of Nutrition and Food Science

English
Telugu

References

References

References

References savailable upon request

Strong Interpersonal Communication
Skills

Knowledge of Anatomy



